(Priya:)in this case, Leonard.
(Priya:)So much for count one.
But...
There's no buts, Sheldon;
that's how the law works.
(Leonard:)Schooled!
(Priya:)As for the shower capacity
issue,
(Priya:)I cite addendum J.
"When Sheldon showers second,
any and all measures
(Priya:)shall be taken to ensure an
adequate supply of hot water."
I believe this supersedes
the occupancy issue.
Superseded!
(Sheldon:)This isn't over.
No offense, but
shower sex with you
is now the second best thing
that's happened today.
(Raj:)Mmm, Greek food
on pizza night?
(Raj:)This is the most delightfully
cruel thing we've done to Sheldon
(Raj:)since we left that fake message
from Stephen Hawking
(Raj:)on his voice mail.
(Priya:)Seriously?
I wish to discuss your theories
of black holes.